The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
The Soul Refining Sect ?
Surround the outer sect gates,
no one is allowed to leave !
This criminal
must be executed on sight !
Yes !
We don't know who did it ?
Who could have caused such a commotion ?
No idea...
I've fully recovered to the peak of Middle stage Nascent Soul.
My Origin Soul has also stabilized.
But I still can't retrieve
the Heaven Defying Bead.
Who exactly is this person ?
If I know but don't report him,
I might be implicated.
Perhaps...
Wang Zhen\NSoul Refining Sect Inner disciple\NEarly stage Nascent Soul
Everyone will be inspected.
Any suspicious movements,
and you will be killed immediately !
Looks like
this is the famous Soul Flag of the Soul Refining Sect.
If I can learn this technique
and refine flags with wandering souls,
the flags wouldn't be weaker than the Restriction Flag.
Spare me !
It's not him.
Continue inspecting !
If it wasn't him,
why did he try to run away ?
Everyone can enter the Outer Soul Refining Sect,
so many disciples have a shady background.
There are also spies
sent by other sects to learn about the Soul Flags.
But under a soul search,
nothing can remain hidden.
Come,
let's go.
Next person !
You.
Next !
Move !
Come.
Next !
He wasn't found out !?
You.
Impossible !
Hurry up !
Alright, next.
You.
The highest cultivation among these Inner disciples
is only Early stage Nascent Soul.
The intricacies of my restrictions
is beyond their comprehension.
To think I could avoid the inner elders' inspection so easily...
Thankfully, I didn't act rashly.
This person...
must be avoided at all costs...
Aside from those with ulterior motives,
nothing related to the matter of last night.
Could it be...
the work of another sect ?
Enough.
The sect competition is approaching.
Go prepare for it !
Yes !
Whether it's the main Spirit Vein
or the Soul Flag refining method,
they're all privileges for Inner disciples.
It looks like
I need to obtain the status of an inner disciple in this competition,
no matter what.
Having survived this near death experience
helped me gain some insight into my domain.
Although my cultivation has only recovered to Peak Late stage Nascent Soul,
the comprehension of my domain
has broken through to Middle stage Soul Formation.
Wang Lin's avatar\NPeak Late stage Nascent Soul
If I can find that main Spirit Vein
then I can breakthrough again.
Now,
celestial spiritual energy
will have a limited effect on the seal.
To keep breaking it,
I'll need another method.
The Tea Domain left by Li Yuanfeng is at early stage Soul Transformation
but it's already this powerful.
This means Soul Transformation cultivators can materialize their domains
far beyond what Soul Formation cultivators can achieve.
Senior Brother...
This aura is...
Senior Brother,
I'm Liu Mei
do you remember me ?
Zhuque Zi's disciple...
Back then, you were that youth from the Heng Yue Sect.
Now...
you've actually become a Soul Refining Sect disciple.
Centuries
aren't enough for you to quietly become the Suzaku's disciple.
Unless...
you always were...
Senior Brother is clever.
Since you came all this way to see me,
what exactly do you want ?
Senior Brother Wang,
I won't hide it
Liu Mei approached you
because I wanted to remember with you.
Your bracelet,
Red Butterfly had the same kind around her wrist.
She is too suspicious,
her intentions are unclear.
She definitely harbors ill will.
That wasn't needed, farewell.
500 years ago,
he was just an ignorant youth.
The current him
has a heart of steel.
But what is
his Dao Heart ?
Sect competition\NSoul Refining Sect
Die !
I surrender !
Surrendering
still means death !
It seems this competition
will claim many lives again.
Only one winner can enter the Inner sect.
Of course they'll fight desperately.
You'll definitely win !
You can do it !
Go for it !
Die !
The Death Spell ?
Interesting...
Each Soul Refining Sect competition,
from the tens of thousands of outer disciples
less than half survive.
Such selection rules are unheard of.
They seems to encourage mutual slaughter.
There must be hidden reasons...
Could it be...
They are making disciples kill each other
to collect their souls ?
So this competition's purpose
is to collect souls for the Inner sect.
I never thought that the Soul Refining Sect's strength
relied on such cruel means.
Final round
One with weird spells
Si Ma\NSoul Refining Sect outer disciple\NLate stage Core Formation
who is bloodthirsty by nature.
And one unremarkable
who stumbled into the finals.
This year's finals
are really boring.
Begin...
Middle stage Core Formation ?
I've practiced this technique for decades,
finally my wish will come true !
Kid,
you were lucky to reach the finals.
But meeting me
is your fate !
Die !
The Death Spell...
Condense !
Your spell
is to kill cultivators of your level
in one strike.
You know the Death Spell ?!
Impossible !
The Death Spell can't fail !
This low-level spell
is just an imitation of the Ji Realm.
If you have a higher cultivation,
it will kill instantly.
But if the gap in cultivation too wide,
it backfires.
Impossible !
What's your real cultivation ?!
Wu Daoqi\NSoul Refining Mountain Grand Elder\NPeak Late stage Nascent Soul
Disciple Wang Zhen
greets Grand Elder.
This is the competition winner,
Qian Mu.
How did you counter
Si Ma's Death Spell ?
I concealed my cultivation,
I'm actually at Peak Late stage Core Formation,
so he couldn't harm me.
He's not lying.
But by relying on a higher cultivation,
you killed a talented prospect...
You there,
you will handle him.
Disciple obeys.
Congratulations Junior Brother
for winning
the Soul Refining Sect competition.
You will come
to Inner sect with me.
These 3 mountains belong to the
Soul Refining Mountain
Soul Refining,
Soul Extracting Mountain
Soul Extracting
and Soul Sealing factions of the Inner sect.
The Inner Spirit Vein
Soul Sealing Mountain
has such abundant spiritual energy...
Can Senior Brother
tell me about Soul Flags ?
Of course.
Soul Flags gain strength
the more souls there are in them.
Ten and Hundred-Soul Flags common.
But if you can create a Thousand-Soul Flag
it will gain special spells.
This is a Thousand-Soul Flag,
I made it
with 1000 souls.
To refine a Thousand-Soul Flag,
you will need a primary soul.
Its strength
must exceed that of all others souls combined.
The more powerful it is,
the more souls can be sealed in the flag.
The souls sealed in the flag
will not dissipate.
This is the foundation
of the Soul Flag refining method.
Although on planet Suzaku
I have seen other types of soul flags,
compared to Soul Refining Sect
they are completely worthless.
These 9 golden rings
are where 9 Soul Formation Elders cultivate.
Nine Golden Rings\NSoul Refining Sect
Junior Brother,
have you heard of Ceng Niu ?
The one rumored to be
the strongest under Soul Transformation on planet Suzaku.
I've heard about him.
Actually, our sect
originally had 10 Soul Formation cultivators.
Years ago, an Elder was traveling
and accidentally clashed with Ceng Niu,
he was killed by him.
When did I kill a Soul Refining Sect's Soul Formation cultivator ?
Ceng Niu disappeared at just the right time.
Ancestor Du Tian was going to personally demand an explanation.
Ancestor Du Tian ?
Our Soul Refining Sect
has 2 Soul Transformation Ancestors.
These 2 blood rings
are where they cultivate.
Ancestor Du Tian's Billion-Soul Flag
could make even Zhuque Zi
think twice before acting.
There are no teachers in the sect,
we cultivate independently.
You've been assigned to the Soul Refining Mountain.
On this mountain,
you may choose any location
to establish your cultivation cave.
Inner disciple robes and token
are distributed in the hall.
Spells
are found in the scripture pavilion.
Thank you Senior Brother Wang.
Scripture Pavilion\NSoul Refining Sect
Token ?
You can enter.
The third floor is off limits.
But you can browse freely
the other 2 floors.
Senior, I want to know
where the Soul Flag manuals are.
Those aren't here
What are you staring at ?
Only 10 Soul Flag jade slips exist.
If you want one
go steal one by force !
Steal it and it's yours.
If you have the strength to kill,
then kill.
See something you like ?
Steal it.
Fancy a female cultivator ?
Just take her.
Take what you want by strength,
that's the law of the Soul Refining Sect !
No rules ?
Complete freedom ?
That's quite an unusual sect...
Brat
You're the fifth in 100 years
that has tried to attack me.
Okay, this old man will play with you !
Grandfather, please stop !
Our Inner sect has another rule.
A rule ?
You can steal,
but if someone surrenders, don't kill them.
Junior Brother,
there's a jade slip right there.
The Soul Refining Sect
has gained another person not to be messed with.
You destroyed my cave,
are you looking for death ?!
Each soul is strong,
some even rival the pressure of Core Formation cultivators.
This Soul Flag is good,
Hundred-Soul Flag
I'll take it.
I surrender !
I surrender...
Jade slip, Soul Flag,
they're yours.
Soul Refining jade slip
I have two concubines too,
take them !
By the rules,
you can't kill me !
While it does contain Soul Flag refining methods,
it seems
this jade is still incomplete.
Xu Jun\NSoul Refining Sect Inner Disciple\NMiddle stage Core Formation
Senior Brother,
did you notice that this Soul Flag method
is flawed ?
You must be Qian Mu,
this year's outer disciple competition winner.
Junior Sister Xu Yun
greets Senior Brother.
The Soul Flag refining method
is flawed because it's split into 3 parts.
They're named after the 3 mountains.
They're called
Soul Refining,
Soul Extracting,
and Soul Sealing.
If you combine all 3
you will get the true Soul Flag refining method.
Don't follow me !
Main Spirit Vein mine\NSoul Refining Sect
The main Spirit Vein's spiritual energy is so dense
that taking a little shouldn't matter.
Could this be...
an ancient soul restriction ?
It uses souls to create restrictions.
Not only is it unpredictable,
but it's even more powerful than ordinary restrictions.
This kind of restriction
must hide a treasure.
There is soul energy inside it
but I don't know if it's a treasure or a curse.
Since I'm in this situation,
I will take the risk.
Break !
Is this...
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.